Hadi Muhsin

UX | Product Design

hadimuhsin.com

+65 9679 0052

hadimuhsin.md@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/hadimuhsin

Skills

UX Methods

User Research
Competitive Analysis
Information Architecture
Customer Journey Mapping
Wireframing
Prototyping
User Interface Design
Usability Testing

Tools

Figma
Sketch
InVision
Zeplin
Botsociety
Adobe CC
G Suite
Microsoft Office

Development

HTML CSS

Organisation

better.sg, *UX Design Volunteer* ☑ November 2020 – present Singapore

Award

Anugerah MENDAKI Award,

Yayasan MENDAKI September 2014

Profile

Curious, methodical and responsible user experience (UX) designer with 2 years of experience. Core competencies include product, agile development process, design research and graphic design. Seeking to work in a great team to make a difference and continue evolving as a UX Designer.

Professional Experience

Product Designer, Ninja Van

February 2020 - present | Singapore

- Collectively streamlined and improved agile development process across product and engineering teams.
- Planned and conducted user research across 6 Southeast Asia markets and generated actionable insights to improve user experience.
- Defined user personas and mapped flowcharts and customer journey maps that are used across teams.
- Developed prototypes and designed interfaces for external products such as Ninja Dashboard and NinjaChat.
- Validated designs through usability testing.
- Designed and standardised Design System documentation.

Design Assistant, *Innosparks Pte Ltd, an ST Engineering Lab* ☑ July 2018 – September 2018 | Singapore

- Prototyped a high-fidelity mobile app for Smart Wheelchair.
- Designed 2 graphic adaptations of print and digital collaterals for products such as AIR+ Kids.

Graphic Designer, Denstu Singapore

March 2017 - August 2017 | Singapore

- Conceptualised and designed advertising campaigns for local and multinational brands (Canon, National Library Board, Sentosa, Subway and Toyota).
- Developed 3 visual assets for pitches with different teams.

Creative Intern, Young & Rubicam Singapore

October 2016 - January 2017 | Singapore

 Applied learning in conceptualising and designing advertising campaigns for local and multinational brands (Caltex, M1, Popeyes, Robinsons and Workforce Singapore).

Education

User Experience Design Immersive Programme Graduate,

General Assembly ♂

October 2019 - December 2019 | Singapore

- Applied learning in user experience (UX) research and design.
- Developed and designed 5 projects ranging from mobile apps to service design with different teams.

Bachelor of Arts in Communication Design, 2nd Upper Class Honours,

Singapore Institute of Technology ☑

September 2017 - June 2019 | Singapore

• Conducted design research on Singapore's Park Connector Network (PCN) wayfinding and developed branding and wayfinding design guidelines.

Diploma in Visual Communication and Media Design (with Merit),

Singapore Polytechnic 🛮

April 2011 - May 2014 | Singapore

- Chairperson for SP Design School's graduation show, Edition 14.8
- Director's Honours List Academic Year 2011/2012